{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "ja",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "1st",
      "answer": "ついたち"
    },
    {
      "question": "2nd",
      "answer": "ふつか"
    },
    {
      "question": "3rd",
      "answer": "みっか"
    },
    {
      "question": "4th",
      "answer": "よっか"
    },
    {
      "question": "5th",
      "answer": "いつか"
    },
    {
      "question": "6th",
      "answer": "むいか"
    },
    {
      "question": "7th",
      "answer": "なのか"
    },
    {
      "question": "8th",
      "answer": "ようか"
    },
    {
      "question": "9th",
      "answer": "ここのか"
    },
    {
      "question": "10th",
      "answer": "とおか"
    },
    {
      "question": "14th",
      "answer": "じゅうよっか"
    },
    {
      "question": "20th",
      "answer": "はつか"
    },
    {
      "question": "24th",
      "answer": "にじゅうよっか"
    },
    {
      "question": "31st",
      "answer": "さんじゅういちにち"
    },
    {
      "question": "30th",
      "answer": "さんじゅうにち"
    }
  ]
}
